Zolazamani Mazibuko

FRONT FND DEVELOPER

Profile

I am a front-end developer who holds an honours degree in electronic engineering and I have an ever growing interest in getting better and delivering quality products. I am experienced with building web applications using React and building out integration solutions in a professional environment. I thrive in all settings that enable collaborative working and transparency.

Employment History

Full-Stack Software Engineer, MethodData

NOVEMBER 2021 — PRESENT

- Accurately converted Figma designs to create web pages for user consumption.
- Debugged various issues using TypeScript, GraphQL, MaterializeCSS and LESS.
- Built fault tolerant, decoupled and cloud based applications using AWS services such as S3, SNS, EC2, Lambda and others.
- · Aided businesses integrate on premises system with CRMs using AWS.
- Used git for CI/CD on all projects.

Front-End Developer/Facilitator, MIC Training and Development

FEBRUARY 2020 — NOVEMBER 2020

- Translated all requests to HTML and CSS requirements/implementation for the learner portal the TVET college was moving to.
- Headed up a facilitation centre as part of my vacation work to get managerial experience with minor oversight.
- Taught and graded content for students for the system development class.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Engineering: Electronic Engineering, University of KwaZulu-Natal

I hold an electronic engineering honours degree with great focus on design, control systems, communications, analogue and digital electronics as well as embedded systems.

I graduated having achieved a distinction in Data Communications as well as Engineering Management & Labour Relations.

Courses/Certificates

AWS Certified Developer Associate, AWS

JUNE 2022 — JUNE 2022

AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials, AWS

Details

Durban, South Africa +27 61 453 9331 zolazamani@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

<u>GitHub</u>

Skills

JavaScript

React

Python

NodeJS

TypeScript

AWS

Git

React JS-Complete Guide for Frontend Web Development, Udemy

OCTOBER 2021 — NOVEMBER 2021

Advance Your Skills in JavaScript, LinkedIn Learning

JUNE 2021 — AUGUST 2021

Introduction to Machine Learning, Duke University via Coursera

MARCH 2021 — APRIL 2021